Let's recap. Today, you moved from discovery to architecture. You took the powerful insights
about yourself and forged them into the first draft of your M.V.P. blueprint, your mission,
vision, and purpose. You were also introduced to the 90-Day Way, the operating system you will
use to execute that blueprint. This is a monumental step. Your homework is to continue
refining your M.V.P. statements in your playbook. Live with them. Put them on. See how they feel.
They don't have to be perfect, but they need to feel true. Read them out loud. Does it sound
like you? This is an iterative process and anticipate several drafts before you anchor
in on your final draft. In our next lesson, we will begin to activate this plan. We'll talk
about conditioning your resilience and agility to overcome the resistance you will inevitably face
as you start to make bold moves. You have your game plan. Now it's time to prepare to execute.
You've got this. Make it happen. When you completed the drills from lesson three
in your playbook, mark the lesson complete. Keep up the momentum. I'll see you soon.